Shannon K. Price

<u>shannonkprice00@gmail.com</u> | 936.404.3348 | Euless, TX 76039 github.com/shannonkprice00 | LinkedIn @Shannonkprice00

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Software developer with education and experience with multiple programming languages, systems, networks and tools. Professional experience serving clients and partnering with internal and external stakeholders to achieve shared organizational goals. Ability to break down complex problems and deliver creative solutions. Reputation for team leadership, attention to detail and time management skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML | CSS | JavaScript | C#

Tech Structures: Object Oriented Programming | MVC Paradigm | Document Object Model | Agile Development | .NET

Front-End Skills: Bootstrap | Google Fonts | jQuery | Day.js | React | Responsive Design | Testing

Back-End Skills: API's | Node.js | Express.js | SQL | Sequelize | MongoDB | Mongoose | REST | GraphQL | Apollo Client |

JSON Web Tokens | Testing

Progressive Web Applications: Webpack | Workbox | Caching | Service Workers

TECHNICAL EDUCATION

Southern Methodist University, Dallas, TX Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp Certification

Certification Earned: August 2023

- Capstone: Created MERN-stack, single-page application leveraging full suite of technology tools learned in the course. The application provided a platform for users to submit written entries, tracked health data, linked to real-world resources, and introduced a social network for comments between users. Technologies used include, React, GraphQL, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Mongoose ODM, Bootstrap Library, JSON Web Tokens.
- Interactive Front-End Application Project: Utilized Node.js, Epress.js to create RESTful API; Handlebars.js, MySQL and Sequelize ORM for database; Cloudinary library for image formatting. Included GET, POST, PUT and DELETE routes. Followed MVC paradigm and authentication via express-session and cookies.
- Interactive Front-End Application Project: Utilized two server-side APIs, Materialize CSS Framework, modals for user interaction. Allowed users to search movie database by various criteria, create lists and store.

Udemy (Online) Certifications to be Earned: October 2023

C# .NET Core 7 with MS SQL Complete Beginner to Master 2023 Certification | C# Masterclass Certification

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Career Sabbatical 5/2021 to Present

Pursue advanced education in software development and cared for family.

Licensed Physical Therapist Assistant, Ensign Services, Richland Hills, TX

8/2017 to 5/2021

Achieved 92% productivity rate, providing care to 7-10 patients daily. Documented services to maximize Medicare payments. Researched treatment and tailored programs to meet clients' needs.

- Developed documentation best practices; paperwork structure used to train team members.
- Collaborated with medical team, social workers and caregivers to plan care.

Rehabilitation Technician, Rehabcare, Irving, TX

4/2014 to 8/2015

Optimized department documentation to minimize errors, pass audits and retain Medicare funds for services. Screened paperwork for staff members, therapists, doctors and nurses. Assisted patient rehabilitation.

EDUCATION

Southwestern Assemblies of God University, Waxahachie, TX | Bachelor of Arts, Music Major